[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Frost"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "We're celebrating all those British institutions of the moment, aren't we?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "celebrating", "all", "those", "British", "institutions", "of", "the", "moment", ",", "are", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "But it doesn't get more British than Sir David Frost.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "it", "does", "n't", "get", "more", "British", "than", "Sir", "David", "Frost", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Why is it so important?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "it", "so", "important", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Well, I think it is partially because the royal family somehow -- I remember a time of Watergate and so on, some people said and friends of mine in the states said, god, I wish we had the same setup you had, where you have a head of state and a prime minister so that you can get rid of the prime minister without rocking the system.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "is", "partially", "because", "the", "royal", "family", "somehow", "--", "I", "remember", "a", "time", "of", "Watergate", "and", "so", "on", ",", "some", "people", "said", "and", "friends", "of", "mine", "in", "the", "states", "said", ",", "god", ",", "I", "wish", "we", "had", "the", "same", "setup", "you", "had", ",", "where", "you", "have", "a", "head", "of", "state", "and", "a", "prime", "minister", "so", "that", "you", "can", "get", "rid", "of", "the", "prime", "minister", "without", "rocking", "the", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nixon"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNP", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "RB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WDT", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "But as you just said, it can actually be quite useful to have an unelected body that has continuity that can control things when they go a little bit awry politically, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "as", "you", "just", "said", ",", "it", "can", "actually", "be", "quite", "useful", "to", "have", "an", "unelected", "body", "that", "has", "continuity", "that", "can", "control", "things", "when", "they", "go", "a", "little", "bit", "awry", "politically", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Yes, because I mean when Nixon, who actually resigned, it was like the flag who was resigning in a way because the president -- even the discredited president, you know, has that aura about him which here you don't have with prime ministers and the rest.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "I", "mean", "when", "Nixon", ",", "who", "actually", "resigned", ",", "it", "was", "like", "the", "flag", "who", "was", "resigning", "in", "a", "way", "because", "the", "president", "--", "even", "the", "discredited", "president", ",", "you", "know", ",", "has", "that", "aura", "about", "him", "which", "here", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "with", "prime", "ministers", "and", "the", "rest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "I mean Tony Blair, 13 year, I think?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "Tony", "Blair", ",", "13", "year", ",", "I", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tony Blair"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "How would you define duty as it affects a member of the royal family?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "define", "duty", "as", "it", "affects", "a", "member", "of", "the", "royal", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "A royal duty in a way is slightly more inbred.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "royal", "duty", "in", "a", "way", "is", "slightly", "more", "inbred", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "And I thought, I'm stuck was a wonderfully modest way of describing becoming the king, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "thought", ",", "I", "'m", "stuck", "was", "a", "wonderfully", "modest", "way", "of", "describing", "becoming", "the", "king", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "And actually, it kind of encapsulates the reality of being a senior member of the royal family.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "actually", ",", "it", "kind", "of", "encapsulates", "the", "reality", "of", "being", "a", "senior", "member", "of", "the", "royal", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "What do you think Diana would have make of his choice of bride and of the sense of duty that he's not accepting, really?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "Diana", "would", "have", "make", "of", "his", "choice", "of", "bride", "and", "of", "the", "sense", "of", "duty", "that", "he", "'s", "not", "accepting", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Well, I think the duty and so on would be an important thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "duty", "and", "so", "on", "would", "be", "an", "important", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "But how do you think Charles has matured from the day that you interviewed him as a teenager there?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "do", "you", "think", "Charles", "has", "matured", "from", "the", "day", "that", "you", "interviewed", "him", "as", "a", "teenager", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "I think he's -- he was always pretty deep, but I mean I think he's gotten much deeper.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "--", "he", "was", "always", "pretty", "deep", ",", "but", "I", "mean", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "gotten", "much", "deeper", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Do you think he gets an unfairly negative wrap, Prince Charles?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "gets", "an", "unfairly", "negative", "wrap", ",", "Prince", "Charles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Prince Charles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "So what in a sense you're saying is that there are certain situations, the Houston plan, or that part of it was one of them, where the president can decide that it's in the best interest of the nation or something and do something illegal?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "in", "a", "sense", "you", "'re", "saying", "is", "that", "there", "are", "certain", "situations", ",", "the", "Houston", "plan", ",", "or", "that", "part", "of", "it", "was", "one", "of", "them", ",", "where", "the", "president", "can", "decide", "that", "it", "'s", "in", "the", "best", "interest", "of", "the", "nation", "or", "something", "and", "do", "something", "illegal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Well, when the president does it, that means that it is not illegal.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "the", "president", "does", "it", ",", "that", "means", "that", "it", "is", "not", "illegal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "By definition?", "question_tokens": ["By", "definition", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Your best poker face on?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "best", "poker", "face", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Poker face, poker face.", "answer_tokens": ["Poker", "face", ",", "poker", "face", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "And -- but I mean it was exhilarating inside that he'd gone that far because one knew that he'd never said it before, but that he damn well believed it, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "--", "but", "I", "mean", "it", "was", "exhilarating", "inside", "that", "he", "'d", "gone", "that", "far", "because", "one", "knew", "that", "he", "'d", "never", "said", "it", "before", ",", "but", "that", "he", "damn", "well", "believed", "it", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Having seen the movie version of your interview, it's one of the best, I would say, movie accounts of a real story I've seen.", "answer_tokens": ["Having", "seen", "the", "movie", "version", "of", "your", "interview", ",", "it", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "best", ",", "I", "would", "say", ",", "movie", "accounts", "of", "a", "real", "story", "I", "'ve", "seen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$2 million"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "$", "CD", "CD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "How much was it you (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "was", "it", "you", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Well, we needed -- we needed $2 million basically.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "needed", "--", "we", "needed", "$", "2", "million", "basically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "I mean, of all the things you've done in your extraordinary career, was that -- does that remain the great high?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "of", "all", "the", "things", "you", "'ve", "done", "in", "your", "extraordinary", "career", ",", "was", "that", "--", "does", "that", "remain", "the", "great", "high", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, I think it was a real landmark, certainly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "a", "real", "landmark", ",", "certainly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "When he came out with those words?", "question_tokens": ["When", "he", "came", "out", "with", "those", "words", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "A sense of -- a sense of euphoria or a joy, I guess.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "sense", "of", "--", "a", "sense", "of", "euphoria", "or", "a", "joy", ",", "I", "guess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Your other personal favorites, the moments you look back on and think, that was amazing?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "other", "personal", "favorites", ",", "the", "moments", "you", "look", "back", "on", "and", "think", ",", "that", "was", "amazing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "CC", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, there are odd lines with some people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "odd", "lines", "with", "some", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Would you say that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "He's the greatest all around entertainer of all time.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "the", "greatest", "all", "around", "entertainer", "of", "all", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "As a present.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "a", "present", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "We're going to have another short break.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "another", "short", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Of all the presidents, who was the most impressive?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "presidents", ",", "who", "was", "the", "most", "impressive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "That's a great question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George H.W. Bush"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "If you could choose one to lead the country you were living in, which one would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "choose", "one", "to", "lead", "the", "country", "you", "were", "living", "in", ",", "which", "one", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "George H.W. Bush.", "answer_tokens": ["George", "H.W.", "Bush", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "?", "question_tokens": ["?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "What do you think of the looming possibility of President Donald Trump?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "looming", "possibility", "of", "President", "Donald", "Trump", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Well, that's going to be interesting, or President Sarah Palin.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "interesting", ",", "or", "President", "Sarah", "Palin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Concord"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Not much progress, is it?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "much", "progress", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "No, absolutely -- it's incredible why the Concord hasn't prevailed, because usually new discovers that work live on.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "absolutely", "--", "it", "'s", "incredible", "why", "the", "Concord", "has", "n't", "prevailed", ",", "because", "usually", "new", "discovers", "that", "work", "live", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ariel Sharon"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Finally, who would you most like to interview in the world that you've never had the chance to interview?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "who", "would", "you", "most", "like", "to", "interview", "in", "the", "world", "that", "you", "'ve", "never", "had", "the", "chance", "to", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "RBS", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, I nearly had an interview with Ariel Sharon.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "nearly", "had", "an", "interview", "with", "Ariel", "Sharon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "TO", ":", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Cyrus the Great because he was the first man ever to -- who used power to alleviate and improve the human condition and not make it worse.", "answer_tokens": ["Cyrus", "the", "Great", "because", "he", "was", "the", "first", "man", "ever", "to", "--", "who", "used", "power", "to", "alleviate", "and", "improve", "the", "human", "condition", "and", "not", "make", "it", "worse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "What was it like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Absolutely overwhelmed.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "overwhelmed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Moscow"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Did you have a warning that she was going to wear one of your dresses?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "a", "warning", "that", "she", "was", "going", "to", "wear", "one", "of", "your", "dresses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "It's quite extraordinary, but on that particular day, I was on a flight to Moscow for the opening of a Reiss store.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "quite", "extraordinary", ",", "but", "on", "that", "particular", "day", ",", "I", "was", "on", "a", "flight", "to", "Moscow", "for", "the", "opening", "of", "a", "Reiss", "store", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Has business been crazy for that dress or similar dresses since Kate Middleton wore it?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "business", "been", "crazy", "for", "that", "dress", "or", "similar", "dresses", "since", "Kate", "Middleton", "wore", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "It's been absolutely extraordinary.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "absolutely", "extraordinary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Middleton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "One a minute?", "question_tokens": ["One", "a", "minute", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "For the first few days, it was one a minute, literally.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "the", "first", "few", "days", ",", "it", "was", "one", "a", "minute", ",", "literally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What was that like for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "How do you think she's doing so far from the style perspective?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "she", "'s", "doing", "so", "far", "from", "the", "style", "perspective", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "There's no question, she has a great sense of style.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "question", ",", "she", "has", "a", "great", "sense", "of", "style", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "What are you seeing so far?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "seeing", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "I think she's still developing her style.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "'s", "still", "developing", "her", "style", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Could there be a moment where she steps out and we see you have a heart attack of excitement?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "there", "be", "a", "moment", "where", "she", "steps", "out", "and", "we", "see", "you", "have", "a", "heart", "attack", "of", "excitement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "I've got to tell you, I was doing a press week in New York last week.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "got", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "was", "doing", "a", "press", "week", "in", "New", "York", "last", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Do you do wedding dresses?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "do", "wedding", "dresses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Not at the moment, but --", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "but", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Will she be wearing one of her own dresses, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "she", "be", "wearing", "one", "of", "her", "own", "dresses", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "This is the interesting thing.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "interesting", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Two billion people watching, isn't she going to think, I'm going to wear one of my own?", "question_tokens": ["Two", "billion", "people", "watching", ",", "is", "n't", "she", "going", "to", "think", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "wear", "one", "of", "my", "own", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I don't know if she's known for this type of clothing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "she", "'s", "known", "for", "this", "type", "of", "clothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "You dressed David Beckham, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "dressed", "David", "Beckham", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Yes, I have, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "have", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Beckham"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "What am I wearing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "am", "I", "wearing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "We're going to do something very traditional, a morning suit.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "something", "very", "traditional", ",", "a", "morning", "suit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "We'll only see you from here to here, right?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'ll", "only", "see", "you", "from", "here", "to", "here", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "TO", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Just go full length.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "go", "full", "length", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["King George III", "Kate"]}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Katie, what have you heard?", "question_tokens": ["Katie", ",", "what", "have", "you", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "The story today is that bets have been placed that the King George III tiara is the tiara that Kate will step out in.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "story", "today", "is", "that", "bets", "have", "been", "placed", "that", "the", "King", "George", "III", "tiara", "is", "the", "tiara", "that", "Kate", "will", "step", "out", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "It's very famous.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "famous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "What do you know right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "know", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "First of all, it is pure speculation as to what she will be wearing on the day.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "it", "is", "pure", "speculation", "as", "to", "what", "she", "will", "be", "wearing", "on", "the", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "How many tiaras does the queen have to either loan or give?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "tiaras", "does", "the", "queen", "have", "to", "either", "loan", "or", "give", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I don't know the exact numbers, but I would guess it's at least a dozen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "exact", "numbers", ",", "but", "I", "would", "guess", "it", "'s", "at", "least", "a", "dozen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Why would it be, other than the fact that queens have wore them before?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "it", "be", ",", "other", "than", "the", "fact", "that", "queens", "have", "wore", "them", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Well, I think the fact that the queen wore it makes it extra special.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "queen", "wore", "it", "makes", "it", "extra", "special", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "You guys actually repaired it, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "guys", "actually", "repaired", "it", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "It would be kind of fitting if it was a Garrard jewel which was on top of her head, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "kind", "of", "fitting", "if", "it", "was", "a", "Garrard", "jewel", "which", "was", "on", "top", "of", "her", "head", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "would be a great combination, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["would", "be", "a", "great", "combination", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "For you guys, one of the top jewelers in the world, how important is it that someone like Kate Middleton wears your stuff?", "question_tokens": ["For", "you", "guys", ",", "one", "of", "the", "top", "jewelers", "in", "the", "world", ",", "how", "important", "is", "it", "that", "someone", "like", "Kate", "Middleton", "wears", "your", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Let's go back to the priceless comment.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "go", "back", "to", "the", "priceless", "comment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Middleton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110426pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Are you excited?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "excited", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]